A Guide to the Papers of Henry Evans Howell, Jr. 1948-1976
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University Libraries, Old Dominion University
- Legal Papers 1948-1966
  - Sub-Series J: S.C.C. Hearings, C & P Telephone
    - S.C.C. Hearing #19152: C & P Telephone Co. Rate Increase Hearing; Correspondence among Interveners August-October 1973 (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 9)
    - S.C.C. Hearing #19152: C & P Telephone Co. Rate Increase Hearing; Post-Hearing Brief by Henry Howell 1973 (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 10)
    - S.C.C. Hearing #19152: C & P Telephone Rate Increase Hearing; Reference; Materials re: Similar Cases 1973 (Box-folder Box 24, Folder 11)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18597: Norfolk & Carolina Telephone Rate Increase Hearing, Application for Increase July 1968 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 1)
  - S.C.C. Hearings, VEPCO
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18867: VEPCO Natural Gas Cut-off Hearing, Miscellaneous Testimony 1970 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 2)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18867: VEPCO Natural Gas Cut-off Hearing, General Correspondence 1970 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 3)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18867: VEPCO Natural Gas Cut-off Hearing, Information from Federal Power Commission 1970 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 4)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18867: VEPCO Natural Gas Cut-off Hearing, Howell Testimony before Hart Committee re: U.S. Senate Bill # 403 (Lee Metcalf-Sponsor) 1971 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 5)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18867: VEPCO Natural Gas Cut-off Hearing, Testimony before Hart Committee re: U.S. Senate Bill # 403 (Lee Metcalf-Sponsor) 1971 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 6)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18897: VEPCO Emergency Rate Increase Hearing, Pleadings by VEPCO 1971 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 7)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18897: VEPCO Emergency Rate Increase Hearing, Miscellaneous Pleadings by Intervener Robert L. Weinberg 1971 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 8)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18897: VEPCO Emergency Rate Increase Hearing, Public Testimony 1971 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 9)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18897: VEPCO Emergency Rate Increase Hearing, Commission Decisions Approving Increase 1971 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 10)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18897: VEPCO Emergency Rate Increase Hearing, Correspondence April-August 1971 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 11)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18897: VEPCO Emergency Rate Increase Hearing, Howell et al Appeal to Va. Supreme Court August-December 1971 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 12)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18897: VEPCO Emergency Rate Increase Hearing, Howell et al Appeal to Va. Supreme Court January, 1972; May 1973 (Box-folder Box 25, Folder 13)
    - S.C.C. Hearing 3 19027: VEPCO Rate Increase Hearing, VEPCO Application
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 19027: VEPCO Rate Increase Hearing, VEPCO Application (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 1)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 19027: VEPCO Rate Increase Hearing, Howell Move for Postponement (Va. Supreme Court) 1971-1972 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 2)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 19027: VEPCO Rate Increase Hearing, Correspondence 1971-1972 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 3)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 19027: VEPCO Rate Increase Hearing, Pre-Hearing Brief of Intervener H. Howell 1972 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 4)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 19027: VEPCO Rate Increase Hearing, Pleadings by Intervener H. Howell 1972 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 5)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 19027: VEPCO Rate Increase Hearing, Intervention by Sierra Club 1972 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 6)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 19027: VEPCO Rate Increase Hearing, Commission Orders 1972 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 7)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 19027: VEPCO Rate Increase Hearing, Petition for Rehearing-Va. Committeed for Fair Utility Rates 1972 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 8)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 19027: VEPCO Rate Increase Hearing, Appeal to Va. Supreme Court by Howell, Brief for Appellant 1972 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 9)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 19027: VEPCO Rate Increase Hearing, Correspondence re: Howell Intervention February 1972 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 10)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 19027: VEPCO Rate Increase Hearing, Correspondence re: Howell Intervention March-April 1972 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 11)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 19027: VEPCO Rate Increase Hearing, Correspondence re: Howell Intervention July-October 1972 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 12)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 19179: VEPCO Natural Gas Rate Increase Hearing, Howell Memorandum 1972 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 13)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 19179: VEPCO Natural Gas Rate Increase Hearing, Testimony and Exhibits for VEPCO 1972 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 14)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 19179: VEPCO Natural Gas Rate Increase Hearing, Testimony by Michael J. Ileo 1972 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 15)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 19179: VEPCO Natural Gas Rate Increase Hearing, Testimony of Alvis Clement and Edward N. Vassar 1972 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 16)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 19179: VEPCO Natural Gas Rate Increase Hearing, Corresondence 1972 (Box-folder Box 26, Folder 17)
    - S.C.C. Hearings: VEPCO Rate Hearings, General Reference, Articles re: Energy Use and Advertising by Utilities 1968-1973 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 1)
    - S.C.C. Hearings: VEPCO Rate Hearings, General Reference, Articles re: Utilities Regulation 1968-1973 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 2)
    - S.C.C. Hearings: VEPCO Rate Hearings, General Reference, Materials re:Detroit Edison Case 1968-1973 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 3)
    - S.C.C. Hearings: VEPCO Rate Hearings, General Reference, Material re: Detroit Edison Case 1968-1973 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 4)
    - S.C.C. Hearings: VEPCO Rate Hearings, General Reference, Materials re: N.Y. Rate Case (Consolidated Edison) 1968-1973 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 5)
    - S.C.C. Hearings: VEPCO Rate Hearings, General Reference, Materials re: Washington D.C., Rate Case (PEPCO) 1968-1973 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 6)
    - S.C.C. Hearings: VEPCO Rate Hearings, General Reference, Articles re: Energy Use and Advertising by Utilities 1968-1973 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 7)
    - S.C.C. Hearings: VEPCO Rate Hearings, General Reference, Material re: Washington D.C., Rate Case (PEPCO) 1968-1973 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 8)
    - S.C.C. Hearings: VEPCO Rate Hearings, General Reference, Decisions by Miscellaneous Public Utilities Commissions 1968-1973 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 9)
    - S.C.C. Hearings: VEPCO Rate Hearings, General Reference, Material re: Energy and Rates 1968-1973 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 10)
    - S.C.C. Hearings: VEPCO Rate Hearings, General Reference, Material re: Energy Use and Rates 1968-1973 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 11)
    - S.C.C. Hearings: VEPCO Rate Hearings, General Reference, Material re: Utilities Regulation and Fair Rates of Return 1968-1973 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 12)
    - S.C.C. Procedural Rules, Compliance with Federal Price Controls 1972 (Box-folder Box 27, Folder 13)
  - S.C.C. Hearings, Auto Insurance Rates
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 17357: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, Miscellaneous Legal Motions 1965 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 1)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 17357: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, Pleading before Va. Supreme Court 1965 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 2)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 17357: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, General Correspondence January-April 1965 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 3)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 17357: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, General Correspondence May 1965 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 4)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 17357: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, General Correspondence June-July 1965 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 5)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 17357: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, General Correspondence August-September 1965 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 6)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 17357: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, General Correspondence October, 1965; March 1966 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 7)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 17680: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, Report of Commission-Hired Actuaries August 1966 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 8)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 17680: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, Brief of Interveners 1967 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 9)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 17680: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, Brief by Defendants 1967 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 10)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 17680: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, Opinion of Commission May, 1967 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 11)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 17680: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, General Correspondence March-August 1966 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 12)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 17680: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, General Correspondence September-December 1966 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 13)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 17680: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing,General Correspondence January-May, 1967 (Box-folder Box 28, Folder 14)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18386: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, Applications for Rate Increase February, 1967 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 1)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18386: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, Testimony, Motions before Commission 1967 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 2)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18386: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, Correspondence, Miscellaneous Material April-June, 1967 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 3)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18386: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, Appeals to Virginia Supreme court, Appellants Briefs (Va. AFL-CIO, Howell) 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 4)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18386: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, Appeal to Va. Supreme Court, Decision April, 1969 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 5)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18386: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, Appeal to Va. Supreme Court, Petition for Rehearing by Appellees May-June, 1969 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 6)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18386: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, Appeal to Va. Supreme Court, Correspondence 1967 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 7)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18386: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, Appeal to Va. Supreme Court, Correspondence 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 8)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18386: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, Rehearing after Va. Supreme Court Overruled Commission's Decision June-September, 1969 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 9)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18386: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, Rehearing by S.C.C., Correspondence May-June, 1969 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 10)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18386: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, Rehearing by S.C.C., Correspondence July-September, 1969 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 11)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18406: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, Application for Increase, Correspondence April-June, 1967 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 12)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18508: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, Correspondence, Testimony, Commission Orders September-November, 1967 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 13)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18615 and 18680: Auto Insurance Rate Hearings, miscellaneous 1968-1969 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 14)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18721: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, Testimony, Motions and Orders October-December, 1969 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 15)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18721: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, Correspondence October-December, 1969 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 16)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18772, 18995, and 19002: Auto Insurance Rate Hearing, Rehearing by S.C.C., Correspondence 1969-1971 (Box-folder Box 29, Folder 17)
  - S.C.C. Hearings, Fire and Casualty, Homeowner's Insurance
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 18946: Fire Insurance Rate Hearing, Correspondence March, 1971 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 1)
    - S.C.C. Hearing # 19000: Homeowner's Insurance Rate Hearing, Commission Order May, 1971 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 2)
    - S.C.C. Insurance Rate Hearings: Fire and Casualty, Reference Material re: Florida and Maryland 1966 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 3)
    - S.C.C. Insurance Rate Hearings: Fire and Casualty, Reference Material re: Florida Hearing (Vol. I) 1966 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 4)
    - S.C.C. Insurance Rate Hearings: Fire and Casualty, Reference Material re: Florida Hearing (Vol II) 1966 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 5)
    - S.C.C. Insurance Rate Hearings: Fire and Casualty, Reference Material re: Fire Insurance Rates in Virginia 1928, 1966 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 6)
    - S.C.C. Insurance Rate Hearings: Fire and Casualty, Reference Materials, Insurance Counsel Journal (April 1964), 1966 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 7)
    - S.C.C. Insurance Rate Hearings: Fire and Casualty, Reference Materials, Insurance Counsel Journal July 1965, 1966 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 8)
    - S.C.C. Insurance Rate Hearings: Fire and Casualty, Reference Materials, Moody's Handbook 1965, 1966 (Box-folder Box 30, Folder 9)
  - I.C.C. Hearing, Norfolk & Western R.R. ( Powhatan Arrow Case)
    - I. C. C. Hearing # 25645: Norfolk & Western R. R. Discontinuance, Motions and Orders May-June, 1969 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 1)
    - I. C. C. Hearing # 25645: Norfolk & Western R. R. Discontinuance, Motions and Orders November, 1969 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 2)
    - I. C. C. Hearing # 25645: Norfolk & Western R. R. Discontinuance,Testimony of L. F. Popp, W.A. Farris, and Cecil Goodrich 1969-1970 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 3)
    - I.C.C. Hearing # 25645: Norfolk & Western R. R. Discontinuance, I.C.C. Final Decision February 1970 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 4)
    - I.C.C. Hearing # 25645: Norfolk & Western R. R. Discontinuance,Correspondence wit I.c.c., May-December, 1969 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 5)
    - I.C.C. Hearing # 25645: Norfolk & Western R. R. Discontinuance,Correspondence re: Howell Intervention May-November, 1969 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 6)
    - I.C.C. Hearing # 25645: Norfolk & Western R. R. Discontinuance,Correspondence from Public Opposing Dropping of Powhatan Arrow May-September, 1969 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 7)
    - I.C.C. Hearing # 25645: Norfolk & Western R. R. Discontinuance, Reference Materials, I.C.C. General Rules of Practice January, 1969 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 8)
    - I.C.C. Hearing # 25645: Norfolk & Western R. R. Discontinuance, Reference Materials, I.C.C. Report "Intercity Rail Passenger Service 1968, 1969 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 9)
    - I.C.C. Hearing # 25645: Norfolk & Western R. R. Discontinuance, Reference Materials, Miscellaneous 1969 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 10)
    - I.C.C. Hearing # 25645: Norfolk & Western R. R. Discontinuance,U.S. District Court in Richmond, Complaint for Injunction May, 1969 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 11)
    - I.C.C. Hearing # 25645: Norfolk & Western R. R. Discontinuance, U.S. District Court in Richmond, Memorandum in Support for Injunction June, 1969 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 12)
    - I.C.C. Hearing # 25645: Norfolk & Western R. R. Discontinuance, U.S. District Court in Richmond Affidavits re: Injunction June,1969 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 13)
    - I.C.C. Hearing # 25645: Norfolk & Western R. R. Discontinuance, U.S. District Court in Richmond, Motions for Dismissal of Suit for Injunction, Dismissal May-June, 1969 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 14)
    - I.C.C. Hearing # 25645: Norfolk & Western R. R. Discontinuance, U.S. District Court in Richmond, Correspondence May,1969 (Box-folder Box 31, Folder 15)
- Political Papers 1948-1973
  - Norfolk 1948-1952
    - General Correspondence 1948-1952 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Francis Pickens Miller Senatorial Campaign: Correspondence, Campaign Materials 1952 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Draft Robert Whitehead for Governor Effort: Correspondence, Campaign Materials, Notes 1953 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 3)
    - General Assembly Campaign: Howell Suit re: Position on Ballot 1953 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 4)
    - General assembly Campaign: Correspondence, Bills 1953 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 5)
    - General Assembly Campaign: Campaign Materials 1953 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 6)
    - General Assembly Campaign: Miscellaneous Materials (Including Map of Norfolk) 1953 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 7)
    - General 1953-1955 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 8)
    - General Correspondence(Excluding Presidential Campaign) 1956 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Presidential Election: Virginia Volunteers for Stevenson and Kefauver, Correspondence 1956 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Presidential Election: Virginia Volunteers for Stevenson and Kefauver, Organizational Manual 1956 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Presidential Election: Virginia Volunteers for Stevenson and Kefauver, press releases, Campaign materials 1956 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 12)
    - General Correspondence 1957 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 13)
    - General Correspondence 1958 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 14)
    - General Correspondence(Excluding General Assembly Campaign) 1959 (Box-folder Box 32, Folder 15)
  - General Assembly Campaign 1959
    - General Assembly Campaign: Campaign Materials-Bumper Stickers (Howell-Childress) 1959 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 1)
    - General Assembly Campaign: Finances-Correspondence, Bills 1959 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 2)
    - General Assembly Campaign: General Correspondence April,1959 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 3)
    - General Assembly Campaign: General Correspondence May-June, 1959 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 4)
    - General Assembly Campaign: General Correspondence July 1,1959 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 5)
    - General Assembly Campaign: General Correspondence July 2-14,1959 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 6)
    - General Assembly Campaign: General Correspondence July 15-31,1959 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 7)
    - General Assembly Campaign: Correspondence re: General Election August-November,1959 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 8)
    - General Assembly Campaign: Hal Bonney Vote Challenge Suit, Correspondence, Pleadings 1959 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 9)
    - General Assembly Campaign: Hal Bonney Vote Challenge Suit, Voting Certificates (Precincts 1-7) 1959 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 10)
    - General Assembly: Hal Bonney Vote Challenge Suit, Voting Certificates (Precincts 21, 21A, 31A, 34A) 1959 (Box-folder Box 33, Folder 11)
  - 1960
    - General Correspondence January-June, 1960 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence July-December, 1960 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Norfolk City Council Race: Suit re: Election Irregularities June,1960 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Norfolk City Council Race: Grand Jury Investigation June, 1960 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Norfolk City Council Race: Miscellaneous Materials 1960 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Presidential Election in Virginia: Correspondence November 1969-July 1960 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Presidential Election in Virginia: Correspondence August, 1960 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Presidential Election in Virginia: Correspondence September, 1960 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Presidential Election in Virgina: Correspondence October, 1960 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Presidential Election in Virginia: Correspondence, Miscellaneous Materials November, 1960 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 10)
  - 1961
    - General Assembly Campaign: Campaign Materials 1961 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 11)
    - General Assembly Campaign: Campaign Materials, Correspondence January-June 1961 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 12)
    - General Assembly Campaign: Election Forms, Miscellaneous 1961 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 13)
    - General Assembly Campaign: Finances-Campaign Bills April-October 1961 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 14)
    - General Assembly Campaign: Finances Expenditures May-October 1961 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 15)
    - General Assembly Campaign: Finances-Fundraising April-July 1961 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 16)
    - General Assembly Campaign: Miscellaneous Lists-Howell Supporters and Potential Supporters 1961 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 17)
    - General Assembly Campaign(Norfolk): Mary Thrasher Candidacy January-July 1961 (Box-folder Box 34, Folder 18)
    - 1961 General Assembly Campaign: Suit for Injunction Re: Campaign Signs (Complaint, Proposed Order), July 1961 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 1)
    - 1961 General Assembly Campaign: General Correspondence, November 1960- March 1961 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 2)
    - 1961 General Assembly Campaign: General Correspondence, April 1961 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 3)
    - 1961 General Assembly Campaign: General Correspondence, May 1961 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 4)
    - 1961 General Assembly Campaign: General Correspondence, June 1- July 11, 1961 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 5)
    - 1961 General Assembly Campaign: General Correspondence, July 12- November 7, 1961 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence, 1961 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 7)
    - 1961 Elections-Norfolk: Calvin Childress, Clerk of Courts Campaign, January-July, 1961 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 8)
    - 1961 Elections- Norfolk: Citizens for Democratic Government, General Correspondence, November-December, 1960 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 9)
    - 1961 Elections- Norfolk: Citizens for Democratic Government, General Correspondence, 1961 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 10)
    - 1961 Virginia Election: General Correspondence re: Democratic Primary, December 1960-June 1961 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 11)
  - 1962
    - General Correspondence, 1962 (Box-folder Box 35, Folder 12)
    - 1962 Norfolk City Council Race: People's Ticket, Campaign Materials - People's Ticket and Opponents, 1962 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 1)
    - 1962 Norfolk City Council Race: People's Ticket, Finances, Bank Account Records, May-September, 1962 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 2)
    - 1962 Norfolk City Council Race: People's Ticket, Finances, Correspondence re: Expenditures, May-October, 1962 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 3)
    - 1962 Norfolk City Council Race: People's Ticket, Finances, Campaign Invoices, April-July, 1962 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 4)
    - 1962 Norfolk City Council Race: People's Ticket, Finances, Correspondence re: Fundraising, April-July, 1962 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 5)
    - 1962 Norfolk City Council Race: People's Ticket, General Correspondence, November-December, 1961 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 6)
    - 1962 Norfolk City Council Race: People's Ticket, General Correspondence, January-April, 1962 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 7)
    - 1962 Norfolk City Council Race: People's Ticket, General Correspondence, May-June, 1962 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 8)
    - 1962 Norfolk City Council Race: People's Ticket, Reference Material re: Norfolk, 1962 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 9)
    - 1962 Norfolk City Council Race: People's Ticket, Miscellaneous Lists of Workers and Supporters, 1962 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 10)
    - 1962 Norfolk City Council Race: People's Ticket, Confidential Lists of Police Duty Rosters (addresses), 1962 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 11)
    - 1962 Norfolk City Council Race: People's Ticket, Miscellaneous Materials, 1962 (Box-folder Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series F: 1963 General Assembly Campaign
    - General Correspondence, 1963 (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 1)
    - 1963 General Assembly Campaign: Howell Campaign Materials, 1963 (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 2)
    - 1963 General Assembly Campaign: Campaign Materials of Howell Opponents, 1963 (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 3)
    - 1963 General Assembly Campaign: Finances, Bank Records, April 1963- March 1964 (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 4)
    - 1963 General Assembly Campaign:Finances, Correspondence Re: Expenditures, Invoices, June-November, 1963 (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 5)
    - 1963 General Assembly Campaign: Finances, Fundraising, April-August, 1963 (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 6)
    - 1963 General Assembly Campaign: Injunction re: Official Ballots, July 1963 (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 7)
    - 1963 General Assembly Campaign: Mailing Lists, Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 8)
    - 1963 General Assembly Campaign: Mailing Lists, Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 9)
    - 1963 General Assembly Campaign: Labor List, 1963 (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 10)
    - 1963 General Assembly Campaign: Volunteers, Lists of Actual or Potential Campaign Workers, 1963 (Box-folder Box 37, Folder 11)